# MUJAHID SHABBAB ALZAHRANI

## **Computer Science**



MujahidAlzahrani@hotmail.com



www.kodanchi.me



@Kodanchi



+966 50 550 4483

(8)

LinkedIn/in/kodanchi

Computer Science graduate with international working experience dedicated to acquire his academic knowledge and work experience to improve the community ethically and professionally. An enthusiast programmer and a self-motivational, hardworking individual who is aiming to take on more responsibility as quickly as possible.



# **Experience**

#### Current Job:

 March 2017 – Present System Analyst, SABIC, Jubail, Saudi Arabia.

#### Summer Practical Training:

• June 2015 – August 2015

International summer internship, working as system level engineer to develop system management tools using node.js framework like Express, Socket.io and Webpack.

Mentor Graphics Headquarter, Portland, Oregon, United States.

#### Previous Jobs:

• Aug 2016 - Feb 2017 (7 months)

Support and develop ad-hoc web systems.

University of Dammam, Dammam, Saudi Arabia

• February 2011 – January 2012 (1 year) Jarir Bookstore, Khobar, Saudi Arabia.



# **Projects**

### • August 2015 - April 2016

ABET Automation System (Graduation Project) from planning and development phases for eight months. The objective of ABET Automation System is to develop a web based product that will assist computer collages in their ABET credential preparation by automating the process instead of the traditional paper approach.

University of Dammam, Dammam, Saudi Arabia.



### Skills

Laravel	Laravel	Communication
MVC	GitHub	Leadership
VUE.js	UI Design	Teamwork
Java	JQuery	Self-motivation
Android	HTML5	Creativity
Java Server Pages	CSS3	
C++	JavaScript	
Node.js	PHP	



### **Education**

 $\bullet 2012 - 2016$ 

Bachelor degree, Computer Science University of Dammam, Dammam, Saudi Arabia.

2007 − 2009

#### **General Science**

Imam Mohammed Bin Saud High school, Dammam, Saudi Arabia.



### Qualifications

- Four solid years in teamwork experience and project management.
- International US-based working experience.
- Extensive communication skills.
- Extensive background in advertising.
- Founding and managing college technology club for two years.
- Organizing local events like Alumni and GIS.
- Participating in several workshops and international courses (Australia leadership development course).



#### **Awards**

•College Star 2016
Awarded as the best student in

college in 2016.

University of Dammam, Saudi Arabia.

Coding Marathon Award 2014
 Certificate of recognition as winner of first place in level 4 in the 3rd annual coding marathon.
 University of Dammam, Saudi Arabia.